[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们添加了很多新方法，因为新方法允许我们
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We added a lot of new methods because new methods allow us
在没有新语法的情况下提供新功能，因此
to provide new functionality without new syntax, and so
那是大部分注意力都去了的地方。
that's where most of the attention went.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们增加了function.bind，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We added function.bind,
这是jQuery一直在推广的东西，它允许您
which was something that jQuery has been promoting that allows you to
将方法转换为函数，以便可以将其用作回调。
turn a method into a function so that you can use it as a callback.
我们添加了string.trim，所以现在我们有了一个方法，它将删除
We added string.trim, so we now have a method which will remove
字符串中的多余空格。
the extraneous whitespace from a string.
这应该从第一天起就出现在语言中，对吗？
This should have been in the language from day one, right?
只是，它不应该花这么长时间才得到它。
And it's just, it shouldn't have taken this long to get that.
我们有-&gt；&gt；扬声器2：两边都要修剪吗？
We've got- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Does it trim on both sides?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：它会修剪两边。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It trims both sides.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们没有打架
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We didn't fight
有足够的需求去做个人，左派和
enough demands to do the individuals, the left and
正确的版本，我还没有听到任何人抱怨它。
right versions, and I haven't heard anybody complain about it.
如果有人知道，也许我们可以进入他的。
If anybody does, maybe we could get into his.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：那么，你调整修剪，现在，它是这样做的吗，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So, you adjust the trim, and, now, is that what it's doing,
或者它实际上只是更多的JS，或者它是在较低的级别中编写的？
or it's actually just more JS, or is it written in a lower level?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这取决于实现，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It depends on the implementation,
它可以写在更低的层次上。
it could be written in a lower level.
所以，这被称为聚脂填充物，也被称为猴子补丁。
So, this is called poly filling, it's also been called monkey patching.
它允许你在系统中插入代码，所以当Brendan最初
It allows you to insert code into the system, so when Brendan originally
设计语言的时候，他只有10天的时间来做这个原型。
designed the language, he only had 10 days to do this prototype.
他被告知，或者他期望如果他的演示不起作用
He was told that, or he expected that if his demo didn't work
网景会做一些更愚蠢的事情。
that Netscape would have done something much stupider.
我不知道那会是什么，我无法想象那会是什么
I don't know what it would have been, I can't imagine what that would have been
但那是他的[INAUDIBLE]所以他只有10天。
but that was his [INAUDIBLE] so he only had 10 days.
他很有信心他不会在十天内把所有的事情都做好，
And he was pretty confident that he wasn't going to get everything right in ten days,
但他们可能需要在现场做些调整。
but they're probably gonna need to be some tweaks in the field.
所以，他把几乎所有的东西都暴露在地块上。
So, he left almost everything exposed on lot.
所以，用正确设计的语言的东西会被锁定或者
So, things which in a properly designed language would be locked down or
完全开放。
completely open.
因此，您可以将内容添加到object.prototype，用于
So, you can add things to object.prototype, for
例如，用真正的语言。
example, in a real language.
你甚至看不到物体原型，
You shouldn't even be able to see object.prototype,
你知道所有的东西都应该密封。
you know all that stuff should be sealed.
他这样做，可能是正确的，因为他认为
And he did that, probably correctly, because he figured
他没有把每件事都做好，总有一天人们会需要修补
he didn't get everything right and someday people were going to need to patch
实时系统，以便使其工作，这正是发生了什么。
the system in real time in order to make it Work which is exactly what happened.
所以在暴露的语言中有所有这些东西，包括这个。
So there's all this stuff in the language which is exposed including this.
如果您获取此代码并在IE 6浏览器或IE 7或IE 8浏览器上运行它。
If you take this code and run it on an IE 6 browser or IE 7 or IE 8 browser.
然后，他们将以与IE 10相同的方式工作，尊重修剪。
Then they will work the same way as IE ten with respect as trim.trim.
现在IE 10可能有它自己的实现它可能是
Now IE ten might have its own implementation of this it might be
本机实现，因此它可能运行得更快。
a native implementation so it might run faster.
所以这个版本IE慢了六个月。
So this version IE six months slower.
我认为这很好，这就是它应该是什么样子
I think that's great that's exactly how it should be
我们添加了一组大的新的or数组方法和
We added a large new set of or array methods and
我真的很喜欢这些设计方法并不完美，但在那里。
I really like these methods of design wasn't perfect but there.
它们足够好，我们可以使用它们，所以大多数这些都是以相同的方式工作的
They're good enough that we can use these so most of these work the same way in that
您将在数组上传递调用一个方法，并传入一个函数和
you'll pass Call a method on an array and pass in a function and
将为数组的每个元素调用该函数，并且
that function will get called for each element of the array and
事情会根据你提供的方法发生。
things will happen based on what method you provide.
因此each方法将继续执行该行为，直到一个函数
So the every method will keep doing that behavior until a function
返回FALSE，当函数返回FALSE时，它会停止这样做。
returns false and when a function returns false then it stops doing that.
这样就可以循环
So that allows you to loop for
一个时间，然后跳出类似于break可能在for循环中所做的事情。
a time and then bail out similar to what break might be doing in a for loop.
筛选器将接受所有返回值。
Filter will take all of the return values.
如果返回值为真，
If the return value is true,
然后将数组的原始元素复制到新数组中。
then the original element of the array will be copied into a new array.
因此，它允许您采用更大的阵列
So it allows you to take a bigger array and
根据每个元素的情况生成一个较小的数组。
produce a smaller array based on what happens for each element.
for each是取代for的东西
For each is the thing that replaces a for
循环它只是去访问每一个我喜欢的元素。
loop it just goes and visits every element I like for each.
IndexOf将执行搜索，因此您可以在类似于以下内容的数组中进行搜索
IndexOf will do a search, so you can do a search in an array similar to
您可以对字符串执行的搜索Last of Searches，即来自后端的数组。
the searching you can do on strings Last of searches, the array from the back end.
地图可能是其中最强大的
Map is maybe the most powerful of them,
它将从该函数获取每个返回值，并将其存储到一个新数组中。
it will take every return value from that function and store it into a new array.
所以你可以做转换和
So you can do transformations and
你可以用地图做选择和很多新的东西。
you can do selections and lots of new things using map.
Reduce将接受一个数组并将其减少到单个值，并且
Reduce will take in an array and reduce it down to a single value, and
它会这样做，你向它传递一个函数，该函数被调用
it'll do that by, you pass it a function that function gets called for
数组中的值对。
pairs of values from the array.
例如，如果您将add函数传递给reduce，您将得到一个总计函数。
For example if you pass the add function to reduce, you'll get a total function.
如果你传递一个乘法函数来归约，你会得到一个乘积函数
If you pass a multiply function to reduce you'll get a product function
然后是从另一个减少的还原权
then there is reduce right which reduces from the other
在数组的末尾，我没有找到任何原因。
end of the array I've not found any reason for that.
我不知道我们为什么这么做，但它就在里面。
I don't know why we did that, but it's in there.
除使用相反的布尔值外，一些与EVER相似。
Some is similar to every except it uses the opposite boolean value.
我们添加了日期现在。
We added Date.now.
以前也是，
So it used to be,
如果你想得到实时时钟，你就必须这样做。
if you wanted to get the real time clock you'd have to do what this is doing.
您将使用默认配置创建一个新的Date对象，并且
You would make a new Date object with the default configuration and
然后提取它的时间。
then extract its time.
所以通常当你得到时间的时候，是因为你想要测量一些东西
So usually when you're getting the time it's because you want to measure something
但是这个获取时间的过程增加了很多延迟和
But this process of getting access to the time adds a lot of latency and
所以你现在可以直接打电话给Date
so you can now call date now directly and
它会给你实时时钟的当前值。
it'll give you the current value of the real time clock.
现在浏览器仍然增加了很多延迟和
Now browsers still add a lot of latency and
操作系统也会增加很多延迟。
operating systems also add a lot of latency.
所以这并不能证明这确实做得更好，但是
So it's not proven that this actually does a better job but But
这并不是JavaScript的错。
it's not so much JavaScript's fault.
现在情况变得更好了
now so that's gotten better
当第一个标准问世时，Netscape和微软不能
when the first standard was made Netscape and Microsoft could not
就描述数据解析工作方式的标准中的语言达成一致。
agree on the language in the standard for describing how date parsing works.
有一个日期构造函数可以接受字符串并
There's a date constructor that can take a string And
然后它可以尝试将该字符串转换为Date、Object。
it can then attempt to turn that string into a date, object.
但他们无法就如何工作的细节达成一致。
But they couldn't agree on the details for how that worked.
所以不是正确的，
So instead incorrectly,
他们同意不同意，完全没有具体说明。
they agreed to disagree by leaving it completely unspecified.
所以没有标准的语言可以向你保证
So there is no language of the standard that gives you a guarantee that
如果您在此表单上传递，则它将解析。
if you pass at this form then it will parse.
这是一种不好的。
Which is kind of bad.
从那时起，ISO提出了一种国际日期格式，
Now since then, ISO has come up with an international date format,
这是相当不错的。
which is pretty nice.
有时称为ISO文本、ISO日期或ISO字符串。
Sometimes called ISO texts,ISO dates or ISO strings.
你有一年，然后是破折号，然后是一个月和一个破折号，以此类推。
Which you have a year then a dash, then a month and a dash and so on.
因此，Date对象现在将生成该形式的字符串。
So the date object will now produce strings in that form.
并且现在保证日期解析器接受该格式。
And the date parsers are now guaranteed to accept that form.
因此，我们现在至少有一种保证可以接受的日期格式。
So we now have at least one date format which is guaranteed to be acceptable.
所以这是我们要尝试的第一个。
So this is the first one we'll try.
如果那个失败了，那么他们将退回到未明确说明的专有产品上。
If that one fails, then they'll fall back on the under-specified proprietary ones.
但至少有一个可以保证奏效。
But at least there's one that's guaranteed to work.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：关于这两个人的问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Question about those two.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以在此之前的ISO格式幻灯片。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So the ISO format slide before this.
所有东西都是UTC时间，而在此之前只有一次，
Everything was getting UTC times whereas just one before so,
如果你做两个ISO字符串。
if you do two ISO string.
你会得到所有基于UTC时间的东西。
You're gonna get everything based on the UTC time.
如果你是datetime.now，你会得到服务器时间吗？
If you datetime.now, are you gonna get server time?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：或运行代码的机器认为它是的时间。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Or the time that the machine that the code is running on thinks it is.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：您得到一个数据对象，它是UTC。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You get a data object which is UTC.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，在数据对象上，有一些基本的时间。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah at the data object have some fundamental time.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那是独立的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That's independent
当前时区的位置都是正确的。
of the current time zone are situated right.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以你得到了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So you're getting
核心价值。
that that core value.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。谢谢你。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay. Thank you.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们将array.isArray添加到我们尝试使用的语言中
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We added array.isArray to the language we tried to
固定类型的，不能有太多的在网络上是依赖的
fix type of and couldn't that there was too much on the web that was dependent on
SO的破碎行为类型相反，我们添加了这个可怕的丑陋的东西，但是
the broken behavior type of so instead we added this horrendously ugly thing but
至少我们学到了这种语言，布兰登实际上已经计算过了
at least we got into that language And Brendan had actually counted
击键，这比表单的类型小。
the keystrokes and this is smaller than the type of form.
所以即使我看起来更糟，它实际上也小了一点。
So even I looks a lot worse, it's actually a little bit smaller.
我设法添加了对象点键，这将给你一个枚举
I managed to add object dot keys which will give you an enumeration of
对象的所有OwnProperty。
all of the Ownproperties of an object.
因此您不会获得继承的方法名称。
So you don't get the inherited method names.
你只得到你可能是的数据成员
You only get the data members which are the thing that you're probably
最关心的是。
most concerned with.
它以数组的形式返回它，这意味着您可以执行
And it returns it in the form of an array which means you can then do for
每一个都在上面，所以这是相当不错的。
each on it and so that's pretty nice.
&gt；&gt；发言人4：这是你提出的吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: You proposed that?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的，我提出的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah I proposed that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：酷，我一直在用它
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Cool, I use that all the time and
那么我确实喜欢.length，只是为了看看这个对象有多大。
then I do like .length just to see how big this object is.
诸如此类的东西。
And stuff like that.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：不客气。&gt；&gt；类：[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You're welcome. &gt;&gt; Class: [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：是的，很好。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yeah, sweet.
&GT；&GT；演讲者3：你之前说过，一些，是一些吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You were talking about earlier there, some, was it some?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的。&gt；&gt；演讲者3：这有什么不同
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yep. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: How is that different
而不是钥匙？
than keys?
键是一个数组。
Keys is an array.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：有些用于在数组上循环。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Some is for looping on an array.
这是每件事的反面。
It's the opposite of every.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：每个都给你所有的值，有些只给你一个。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Every gives you all the values, some gives you only one.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：每个都给你
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Every gives you
只要函数返回true，一切都会发生。
everything as long as the functions are returning true.
还有一些继续工作，只要一切都是假的。
And some keeps working as long as everything is returning false.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：它对值而不是键进行操作。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's operating on the values not the keys.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：关于基于函数的返回值
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: On the return values that are based on the function
也就是处理密钥。
that is processing the keys.
是啊。&GT；&GT；演讲者6：回到那里的日期，
Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Back on the dates there,
有一个问题。
there is a question.
是否有针对可变日期对象的计划？
Are there any plans for mutable date objects?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：不可变的日期对象？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Immutable date objects?
&GT；&GT；演讲者6：是的，我不知道他的意思是什么。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Yeah I don't know what he means by that.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们将要冻结你可以冻结任何日期对象
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We're going to get to freeze you can freeze any date object
这是他想要的吗？
is that what he wants?
&gt；&gt；扬声器6：我等着呢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: I'm waiting.
我只是想要求澄清请继续。
I'm just going to ask for clarification just go on.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我还设法获得object dot create Object.create
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I also managed to get object dot create Object.create
是使新对象继承自另一个对象的基元。
is the primitive which makes a new object that inherits from another object.
在原型语言中，这应该从第一天起就在语言中。
In a prototypal language, this should have been in the language from day one.
所以我们用新的和.原型的奇怪的东西，
So instead we had the weird thing with new and .prototype.,
所以这给我们提供了一种直接的方式来进行原型继承，这是很好的。
so this gives us a direct way of doing prototype inheritance, which is good.